I get it.
A lot of y'all's identities are attached to,
attached to things that you have decided to believe in.
Not like yourself,
but you want to believe in like the United States.
You want to believe in your religion.
You want to believe in Democrats.
You want to believe in your black identity.
You want to believe in all of these things
that were pretty much made up.
Because the things that are real, you don't believe in.
You know, like nature.
You don't believe in that.
And so I get it.
I get it.
I get why there is such a deep,
you know,
pushback and disdain
for doing something different.
I just watched a black man sit up on this internet
and say that white leftists are the equivalent
to white nationalists.
Mm-hmm.
I sure did.
Said it with his chest,
with some yellow sunglasses on.
Said he was saying something.
Okay.
That man thought he was really putting y'all on to something.
I did a post
where I said,
candidates show up
to run
and it is our job
to push them
to reflect
the constituency.
And people
still said,
well then who are we supposed to vote for?
They still said that.
So I find it
odd.
But then I understand.
I get it.
And I hope y'all get it sooner than later.
I hope you do.
Because man,
it is,
it is unfortunate.
And I tell you,
when I see so many black folks
or what,
what seem like black folks
because it could be bots
going along with the nonsense,
I'm like,
the way that y'all love Jasmine Crockett
for no reason
other than she has said
some like
slick shit
to President Trump
is
bonkers to me.
Bonkers.
I would see,
I could see if you believe,
I could see if you were like,
oh,
she,
I could see if she was starting
a standup career
and y'all were like,
I'm going to support her
because you've seen proof
that she is witty.
So like,
that makes sense.
I get that you like her
because she,
she doesn't mean lace front.
She does.
You know,
I get that.
she,
she has
the same skin color
as folks.
Like,
I can,
I can see the,
the,
the math in that way.
But then again,
y'all was rocking with Kamala
and she wasn't none of that.
So,
I'm just like,
what do you mean
she has common sense?
Is,
is that the bar?
That's the bar.
She has common sense.
Man,
she has common sense.
And thank you,
Val knows it all.
She is a Zionist.
So she does not have common sense.
And I want you all to understand
that nobody who is going
into these spaces,
echoing the sentiments
of the oppressor
is going to be of any use to you.
Not a single one.
And even if
she has the ego
to think
that she will be the one
to be able to walk the line,
she is wrong.
And there is nothing
that she has demonstrated to you
that would make you think,
or that should make you think,
that she does.
It is very easy to push back
against Donald Trump
and Marjorie Taylor Greene.
It is very easy.
They are the lowest
of hanging fruit.
Then you have
James Tallarico.
James Tallarico
is in
Texas
and
he has done
very good
at pushing back
in Texas
against
various bills
and he will
loudly call them
racist.
You know,
he will call them
an overreach
of
religion,
et cetera.
And
both of them
have taken money
from Israel
and
I think
the one thing
that I
I think the thing
that I want
people to really
just
stop doing
is
speaking
so ardently
about things
they don't know.
So like if the topic
is Israel
and
you don't know
anything about Israel
how could
how do you
find it
prudent
to sit up
and say
it doesn't matter
that they have
alignment with Israel.
I don't know
I don't understand
that math.
That's what I'm saying.
If the topic
was NASCAR
and
the beef
that people
had with them
was that they
are invested
in NASCAR
I would have
to sit it out
because I don't
know nothing
about NASCAR.
So I'd have
to sit it out
and say
well let me go
and let me go
and take a look
at NASCAR
and understand
because I can't
I can't
I don't know
enough about NASCAR
to say that NASCAR
ain't a problem.
but this is a
U.S.
problem.
This is an
American
problem.
The culture
of arrogant
ignorance
is the
American
problem.
It is why
so many
of you
who cannot
find a way
out of this
country
will get
swallowed
up by it
because your
peers
fellow
citizens
have been
effectively
convinced
that
they
are smarter
than they are.
They know
they haven't
read no books.
They know
they don't
watch
news.
They know
they haven't
done any
research
and yet
they are
confident.
Confident.
And the
same ones
that told
you
four years
ago
not to
take vaccines
because the
government
are the
same ones
who will
tell you
now
well we
only have
two options
so what
do you
expect?
Start figuring
out who
your people
are y'all.
Start figuring
out who
your people
are
because
it's going
to be
really really
hard to
be in
community
just by
juxtaposition
of where
you live
with folks
who have
such deeply
disparate
values.
You know
what I'm
saying?
Like that's
going to
be hard.
They're
going to
sell you
down the
river
every time.
I drew
this.
They're
going to
sell you
down the
river
and it's
going to
be a real
doozy.
It's going
to be a
real doozy.
so man
I hope
for y'all's
sake that
you find
another path
forward than
these people
because
there's
a lot
of insight
and input
on this
internet
but there's
a lot of
idiots
and they
can really
misguide
you in
a real
way.
Like watching
people call
leftists,
call liberals
leftists is
like what
are you
talking about?
And I
promise you
because I
just started
asking people
like what's
a leftist
and they
get stuck.
Like what
can you
tell me
anything about
Israel?
anything.
They get
stuck.
It's
disconcerting
to be quite
honest.
So
yeah
I just
man
find it
really
encouraging
however
to see
folks
actually
not just
being able
to say
this don't
line up
but being
able to
illuminate
why.
Well you
know so
this guy
right here
Basanders
said one
thing we're
fighting is
the money
backing
these folks.
It's hard
to market
and push
the people
we want
when they
all own
media.
And I
wouldn't
agree with
that.
It's hard
to market
the same
way that
they do.
Yeah.
However
I don't
think it
actually is
that difficult
to market
people
on a
grassroots
level if
you're
actually
tapped into
the
grassroots
level.
But someone
like a
Jasmine Crockett
to my
knowledge
is not.
and I
think when
you're
talking about
marketing
you're
talking
about
and correct
me if
I'm wrong
you're
talking about
marketing
to the
voting
block
when the
voting
block
is not
who
elects
people.
We
suggest
when we
vote we
are a
suggestion.
You trying
to tell me
that Greg
Abbott is
going to
let
Jasmine
Crockett
be a
senator
for Texas?
You crazy.
The fact
that y'all
think these
elections are
not rigged
is beyond
my scope
of comprehension.
Truly.
They let
Zoran
Mamdani
win.
They let
him win.
They are
rioting
in Honduras
right now
because the
U.S.
played with
their election.
That's what
this country
does.
I would
take a
nap before
this book
talk.
Y'all
stay up.